glocalincome.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy

ClubShop Privacy Policy

We understand that when you are doing business online you need to trust the people with whom you are doing business. We take this trust very seriously, and make it a priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information ("PI") you provide us. (PI includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address.) Therefore, as a visitor to ClubShop you have the right to understand our information privacy policies before providing the ClubShop with any of your PI.

ClubShop collects PI that you voluntarily provide to us as well as certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page at ClubShop.com. This technical information is collected from your computer's web browser and may include your IP address, operating system, web browser software (i.e. Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), screen resolution and referrer web site.

ClubShop may share your contact information with your originating sponsor or a sponsor assigned to you (name, ID number, email address, mailing address, and phone number) and your upline and/or downline Team for communications (name, ID number and e-mail address) and our authorized product and service providers as necessary in order to complete a transaction that you specifically request.

There are places throughout ClubShop.com websites that may link you to other web sites that do not operate under ClubShop information privacy practices. When you click through to these web sites, ClubShop's information privacy practices no longer apply. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements for all third party Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. These third party websites include, but are not limited to ClubShop.com Mall Stores, Service Providers, Vendors, and RSS feed sites we may have on our site for your convenience.

ClubShop may be required by law to disclose information you have provided us. ClubShop may also disclose information against someone who poses a threat to ClubShop's interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could bring harm to others.

ClubShop provides you with the means of updating or correcting any PI stored in your "My Account" webpage.

To ensure the confidentiality of your PI, ClubShop uses leading security technology and procedures. When you submit personal information on ClubShop.com, your data is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology certified by a digital certificate from Thawte Server CA. To view this site certificate on each secured page (a page which begins with "https"), click on the image of the closed lock or the solid key on the bottom bar of your browser window. A small frame displaying site security information will pop up.

By providing you with this Privacy Statement, ClubShop is pledging our continued commitment to protecting the information you provide us. Your privacy is important to us. Questions regarding this statement should be sent via postal mail to ClubShop, 955 Morisson Ave, Englewood, FL USA 34223. or e-mailed to ClubShop at [legal@clubshop.com](mailto:legal@clubshop.com?Subject=Privacy_Policy)
